[{"answer": "Well, it all ended with us not getting any gas.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "And how does it all end?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, there's a lot of emotion, there's just thousands of volunteers out here.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "How are you seeing it down there on the ground?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I think he's done extremely well in terms of his sympathy and empathy for the groups, his visit.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "And as a former commander yourself, how do you think the president's done this week in terms of his role as commander-in-chief in what was really a national crisis?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I thought it was a fair appraisal.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Were you pleased that the marathon was canceled?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Last time I checked, Piers, he's the commander-in- chief.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "When you said that some American lives may have been lost because of incompetence, do you lay the blame squarely at the president's door?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "They either were aware of it and decided not to do anything or they were asleep at the switch.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "ORGAN: Do you believe, as some Republicans do, that the White House or certainly people close to the White House were aware of what was happening on that fateful night and decided not to do anything?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, I was in Staten Island this morning, actually.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Did you change your opinion when you saw that overnight and this morning, or were you still of the view, you know what, we should get on with it?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "I don't know what the heck he was doing in Nevada while people were still being discovered dead in New York.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Do you think the president has been an outstanding leader?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't go that far at all.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "President hasn't been to New York.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Should he now come to New York, the president?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Either one can win without Ohio.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Can Mitt Romney become president realistically if he doesn't win Ohio?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "General?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I had to assume.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "The moment that happened on Monday night, did you think and assume that the race would get canceled?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "I was actually a little bit shocked.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "When you heard that it was going ahead, what did you feel?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's probably the right decision, but it seems to be the wrong timing.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I have no horse in this race.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Michael, what do you think?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "ORGAN: I think if the people of London, if we had had one of these --", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Would Churchill have canceled the marathon?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "RIMM: You know, I don't know exactly.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Why has it been so belated, the help that you so desperately need?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the mayor did the right thing.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "What is your reaction to Mayor Bloomberg canceling the marathon?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, first, let me say that my heart goes out to the people on Staten Island and the people up and down the Eastern Seaboard.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "And what reassurance can you give the people there now that they're getting your full attention?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "They can visit our website, RedCross.org, or they can call 1-800-RED-CROSS.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "If people are watching and wish to contribute to the Red Cross for this, what's the best way of doing that?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Certainly Rudy Giuliani is a guy to be able to talk about this honestly.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "I've got to stand right there with the people suffering?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Barack Obama.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Michael Wolff, who is going to win this election?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "121102pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Were you surprised by the sheer scale of the enthusiasm that Christie showed?", "qSentId": 532}]